newzealandgirls.co.nz 2018-12-23

# Escorts | NZ Girls

#### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This Privacy Policy has been written to describe the conditions under which this web site is being made available to you. The Privacy Policy discusses, among other things, how data obtained during your visit to this web site may be collected and used. The Privacy policy also describes how your data is processed and what rights and obligations you have.

By using this web site, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy – if you do not agree please leave the site immediately.

The process of maintaining a web site is an evolving one, and NZGirls may decide at some point in the future, without advance notice, to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your use of the web site, or materials obtained from the web site, indicates your assent to the Privacy Policy at the time of such use. The effective Privacy Policy will be posted on the web site, and you should check upon every visit for any changes.

#### Links to Third Party Web Sites

NZGirls' web sites may provide links to third-party web sites. If you access those links, you will leave NZGirls' web site (eg newzealandgirls.co.nz.) NZGirls does not control these third-party websites and cannot represent that their policies and practices will be consistent with this Privacy Policy. For example, other web sites may collect or use personal information about you in a manner different from that described in this document. Therefore, you should use other web sites with caution, and you do so at your own risk. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any web site before submitting personal information.

#### Types of Information We Collect:

##### Non-Personal Information

Non-personal information is data about usage and service operation that is not directly associated with a specific personal identity. NZGirls may collect and analyze non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use NZGirls’ web sites.

##### Aggregate Information

NZGirls may gather aggregate information, which refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after our site), the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. For example, when you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns and for purposes of system administration.

##### Log Files

Every time you request or download a file from the web site, NZGirls may store data about these events and your IP address in a log file. NZGirls may use this information to analyze trends, administer the web site, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use or for other business purposes.

##### Cookies

Our site may use a feature of your browser to set a “cookie” on your computer. NZGirls' web sites can then read the cookies whenever you visit our site. We may use cookies in a number of ways, such as to save your favorites and passwords so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, to deliver content specific to your interests and to track the pages you’ve visited. These cookies allow us to use the information we collect to customize your experience so that your visit to our site is as relevant and as valuable to you as possible.

Most browser software can be set up to deal with cookies. You may modify your browser preference to provide you with choices relating to cookies. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, certain of the functions and conveniences of our web site may not work properly, and you may be unable to use those of NZGirls' services that require registration in order to participate, or you will have to re-register each time you visit our site. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the “Help” section of the toolbar. We do not link non-personal information from cookies to personally identifiable information without your permission.

##### Personal Information

Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. NZGIRLS.co.nz does not gather any personal information ourselves. Our payments are processed by 3rd party credit card processor Flo2Cash who may require you to enter information about your credit / debit card and Name. This information is not shared with us and we do not store or collect your personal information (name, address, credit card number)

Types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs, passwords, billing information.

#### How We Use Your Information

NZGirls may use non-personal data that is aggregated for reporting about NZGirls' web site usability, performance, and effectiveness. It may be used to improve the experience, usability, and content of the site.

Credit card information is not collected by NZGIRLS.co.nz All payments are processed by Flo2Cash and this data is not shared with NZGIRLS. Credit card numbers are used only for processing payment and are not used for other purposes. NZGIRLS might send you promotional emails or marketing information. As soon as you enter a profile you agree, that NZGIRLS.co.nz will send you information about our services, your account or other information that NZGIRLS.co.nz deems right.

#### Information Sharing

NZGirls does not sell, rent, or lease any individual’s personal information or lists of email addresses to anyone for marketing purposes, and we take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of this information.

We also reserve the right to release personal information to protect our systems or business, when we reasonably believe you to be in violation of our Terms of Use or if we reasonably believe you to have initiated or participated in any illegal activity. In case of illegal activity or request from the police, the operator will share this information with the authorities in case of a court order or a request from the authorities.

In addition, please be aware that in certain circumstances, NZGirls may be obligated to release your personal information pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or other orders.

In keeping with our open process, NZGirls may maintain publicly accessible archives for the majority of our activities.

If you are a registered member of an NZGirls website or email list, you should be aware that some items of your personal information may be visible to other members and to the public. NZGirls' member databases may retain information about your e-mail address, and such other personal address and identifying data as you choose to supply. That data may be visible to other of NZGirls' members and to the public. Your name, e-mail address, and other information you may supply also may be associated in NZGirls' publicly accessible records. (e.g when you post an advertisement and choose to share your details with the public)

Please remember that any information (including personal information) that you disclose in public areas of our web site, such as advertisements and profiles becomes public information that others may collect, circulate, and use. Because we cannot and do not control the acts of others, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose information about yourself or others in public forums such as these.

Given the international scope of NZGirls websites, personal information may be visible to persons outside your country of residence, including to persons in countries that your own country’s privacy laws and regulations deem deficient in ensuring an adequate level of protection for such information. If you are unsure whether this Privacy Policy is in conflict with applicable local rules, you should not submit your information.

If you do not want your personal information collected and used by NZGirls, please do not visit NZGirls' web site or apply for membership of any of NZGirls' websites or email lists.

#### Security

NZGirls make every effort to protect personal information by users of the web site, including using firewalls and other security measures on its servers. No server, however, is 100% secure, and you should take this into account when submitting personal or confidential information about yourself on any web site, including this one. Much of the personal information is used in conjunction with member services such as collaboration and discussion, so some types of personal information such as your name, company affiliation, and email address will be visible to other NZGirls' members and to the public. NZGirls assume no liability for the interception, alteration, or misuse of the information you provide. You alone are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please use care when use access this web site and provide personal information.

#### Opting Out

From time to time NZGirls may email you electronic newsletters, announcements, surveys or other information. If you prefer not to receive any or all of these communications, you may opt out by following the directions provided within the electronic newsletters and announcements.

If you have questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us.

#### Accessing your personal information

You can access your personal information or request the information collected by you any time by emailing nzgirls to info@newzealandgirls.co.nz . NZGIRLS follows European Union data protection and privacy laws as well as the New Zealand law in regards to privacy.
